Guide to the Lawrence A. Brown Papers, 1963-2004 RG.40.351
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
Lawrence A. Brown Papers
1963-2004
RG.40.351
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
6.0 Cubic feet
(5) cartons
The Lawrence A. Brown Papers contain Brown's published works and associated correspondence, mainly on urban geography research, from 1963-2004. Lawrence Brown was a professor and chair of the Department of Geography at Ohio State University.
Brown, Lawrence A., 1935-
Arrangement of Materials
Materials are arranged in the order received.
Acquisitions Information
Accession Number UA.2014.0228: Lawrence A. Brown, 2014
Access to Materials
Materials in this collection are available for patron research, but may be used only in the University Archives Reading Room. Audiovisual materials may need a use copy produced before access is allowed. Some materials in this collection may be stored off-site, and are only available if requested 72 hours in advance of your visit. Contact the University Archives for more information.
Biographical Note
Lawrence A. Brown (1935-2014) was a professor and chair of the Department of Geography at Ohio State University. His scholarship interest focused on spatial processes of innovation diffusion, migration, mobility and urban and housing developments.
Scope and Contents
The Lawrence A. Brown Papers contain Brown's published works and associated correspondence, mainly on urban geography research, from 1963-2004.
Related Materials
Ohio State University Archives Biographical File
Lawrence A. Brown
Brown, Lawrence A., 1935-; Ohio State University--Faculty.; Ohio State University--History.; Ohio State University. Department of Geography.; College teachers--Ohio--Columbus; Urban geography--Research--Ohio--Columbus
- Accession Number UA.2014.0228, 1963-2004; 6.0 Cubic feet; (5) cartons
  - The first assessment: research in geographic education, 1997 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter of the Association of American Geographers, 1996-1997 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 2)
  - Gender, Migration, and the Organization of Work Under Economic Devolution: Ecuador 1982-1990, 1998 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 3)
  - Urban system development, Ecuador's Amazon, Generalization. Frontiers in Regional Development, 1996 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 4)
  - "Continuity and change in an Old Industrial region: The Ohio River Valley", 1982 and 1990 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 5)
  - "The Uprooting of People, Migration, and Labor Force Experiences: Ecuador", 1982 and 1990 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 6)
  - Frameworks of Urban System Evolution in Frontier Settings. Geography Research Forum, 1994 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 7)
  - Urban System Evolution in Frontier Settings. Geographic Review, 1994 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 8)
  - Frontier Migration as a Multi-Stage Phenomena. Papers in Regional Science, 1994 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 9)
  - Causes of Tropical Deforestation in Ecuador. World Development, 1992 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 10)
  - Complementary Perspective, Means of Understanding Regional Change: Frontier Settlement in Ecuador Amazon. Environment and Planning, 1992 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 11)
  - Innovation Diffusion: Retrospect and Prospect. Geography, 1990 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 12)
  - Migrant Fertility differentials: Ecuador. Geografiska Annaler B, 1989 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 13)
  - Polar Reverse, Migration Shifts, Human Resource Profile: Venez, 1987 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 14)
  - Module of Department Specialty of Population, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 15)
  - Population Geography. Geography in America, 1989 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 16)
  - Location, social Category, Individual Labor Market Experiences: Venezuela. International Regional Science Review, 1989 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 17)
  - Reflections, Third World Devel. Economic Geography, 1988 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 18)
  - Policy Aspect Development, Individual Mobil: Mig-Circ, Ecua Rural Sierra. Economic Geography, 1988 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 19)
  - Development Related Context Effects, Individual Attribution, Migration: Venezuela. Demography, 1987 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 20)
  - Migration, Human resource transfer, development context: Logit Analy, Venez, 1987 (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 21)
  - Structural tension, migration and development: A Case Study of Venezuela, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 22)
  - The field of family planning: A Review and New Conceptual Framework, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 23)
  - Rural non-farm employment and migration: evidence from Costa Rica: Socio-Econ Plan. Sci., undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 24)
  - Cross national tests of a 3rd world development-migration paradigm: w/part attention to Venezuela, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 25)
  - Spatial variation in migrant processes and development. A Costa Rican Ex. Of Conv. Modeling Augmented by the Expan. Method: Demography, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 26)
  - Rural destined migration in 3rd world settings: a neglected phenomenon? Regional Studies, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 27)
  - Circulation and Migration in 3rd World Settings: A Comparison in Ecuador. Revista Geografica, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 28)
  - "The dissemination of public sector innovations with relevance to regional change in the United States" in The Regional Economic Impact of Technological Change, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 29)
  - Migration in 3rd world settings, uneven development and conventional modeling: a case study of Costa Rica, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 30)
  - Development Aspects of Migration in 3rd World Setting A Sim., With Implications for Urbaniza., undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 31)
  - Development Related Context. Effects and Individual Attributes in 3rd World Migration. Processes a Venezuelan Ex.: Migration Development in Third World Settings #27, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 32)
  - Circulation and Migration in Third World Settings: A comparison in Ecuador: Migration/Development In Third World Settings #26, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 33)
  - Structural Tension, Migration, and Development: A Case Study of Venezuela: Migration/Development In Third World Settings #24, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 34)
  - Rural-Non Farm Employment and Migration: Evidence From Costa Rica: Migration/Development In Third World Settings #23, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 35)
  - Amplifications Toward A Third World Development-Migration Paradigm; Migration/Development In Third World Settings #22, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 36)
  - Migration, Human Resource Transfers, and Development Contexts: Logit. Analysis of Venezuelan Data #21, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 37)
  - Migration, Planned Growth, and Human Resource Variations Within Third World Urban Systems: A Venezuelan Study: Migration/Development In Third World Settings #20, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 38)
  - The Rural-Urban Interface in Third World Settings: A Discussion of Current Issues: Migration/Development In Third World Settings #17, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 39)
  - Rural Destined Migration in Third World Settings: A Neglected Phenomenon: Migration/Development In Third World Settings #14, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 40)
  - Development Effects Upon Migration in Third World Settings: Conventional Modeling with spatially Varying Parameters via the Expansion Method: Migration/Development In Third World Settings #13, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 41)
  - Migration in Third World Settings, Uneven Development, and conventional Modeling: A Case Study of Costa Rica: Migration/Development In Third World Settings #12, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 42)
  - Development Aspects of Migration in Third World Settings: A Model With Implications for Urbanization: Migration/Development In Third World Settings #6, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 43)
  - Toward a Development Paradigm of Migration: with Particular Reference to Third World Settings: Migration/Development In Third World Settings #1, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 44)
  - Data Resources for NSF-supported Study on the Interrelationships Between Migration and Development in Latin America, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 45)
  - The Location of Urban Populations Service Facilities: A Strategy and Its Application. Social Science Quarterly, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 46)
  - Diffusion in a Growth Pole Context: A Comment. Proceedings of the commission on Regional Aspects of Economic Development of the IGU, Vol. 2: Spatial Aspects of the Development Process, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 47)
  - Innovation in a Developing Economy: A Meso Scale View. The Journal Revista Geografica, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 48)
  - Diffusion Waves Within the context of Regional Economic Development. Journal of Regional Science, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 49)
  - Simmar: A Markov Chain Based Program for the Diffusion of Innovation. Computer Applications, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 50)
  - The Market and Infrastructure Context of Adoption: A Spatial Perspective on Diffusion of Innovation. Economic Geography, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 51)
  - The Diffusion of Cable Television in Ohio: A Case Study of Diffusion Agency Location Patterns and Processes of the Polynuclear Type. Bulletin of Business Research The Ohio State University, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 52)
  - The Diffusion of Cable Television in Ohio: A Case Study of Diffusion Agency Location Patterns and Processes of the Polynuclear Type. Economic Geography, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0001, Folder 53)
  - Diffusion Dynamics: A Review and Revision of the Quantitative Theory of the Spatial Diffusion of Innovation, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 1)
  - Diffusion Processes and Location: A Conceptual Framework and Bibliography, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 2)
  - Perspectives on Urban Spatial Systems, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 3)
  - Studies in Spatial Diffusion Processes, 1: Empirical Considerations., undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 4)
  - Ph.D Dissertation: Diffusion Dynamics: A Review and Revision of the Quantitative Theory of the Spatial Diffusion of Innovation, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 5)
  - Towards a Development Paradigm of Migration with Particular Reference to Third World Settings: Migration Decision Making, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 6)
  - A Simulation Model of Migration and Development: Modeling and Simulation, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 7)
  - Towards a Development Paradigm of Migration with Particular Reference to Third World Settings: Terra, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 8)
  - On the Interrelationships Between Development and Migration Processes: Geographic Research on Latin America, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 9)
  - Information Source Usage in the Migration Decision: Socio-Economic Planning Sciences, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 10)
  - Place Utility, Attribute Tradeoff, and Choice Behavior in an Intra-Urban Migration Context: Socio Economic Planning Sciences, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 11)
  - A Spatial View of Intra-Urban Migration Search Behavior: Socio-Economic Planning Sciences, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 12)
  - Market Penetration and Locational Conflict in Franchise Systems: Decision Sciences, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 13)
  - Perspectives on Innovation Diffusion: Dissemination and Utilization of Alcohol Information, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 14)
  - Innovation Diffusion and Entrepreneurial Activity in a Spatial Context: Research in Marketing, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 15)
  - The Innovation Diffusion Process in a Public Policy Context: Innovation Research and Public Policy., undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 16)
  - Simulating the Spatial Diffusion of Innovation: A Gaming Experimental Approach: Socio-Economic Planning Sciences, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 17)
  - Innovation Diffusion and Development in a Third World Setting: the Cooperative Movement in Sierra Leone. Social Science Quarterly, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 18)
  - "The Innovation Diffusion Process in a Public Policy Context" The Diffusion of Innovations: An Assessment., undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 19)
  - Pesquisas de Difusao em Geofrafia. Tendencias Atuais Na Geografia Urbano/Regional: Teorizacao E Quantificacao, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 20)
  - The Diffusion of Community Innovations: A Conceptualization and Empirical Analysis. Urban Affairs Quarterly, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 21)
  - Spatial Diffusion of Innovation: A Gaming Approach. Simulation and Games, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 22)
  - Promar: The New Product Marketing Game. Computer Applications, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 23)
  - Strategies for the Promotion and Diffusion of Consumer Goods and Services: An Overview. International Regional Science Review., undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 24)
  - Diffusion Agency Strategies and Innovation Diffusion: A Case Study of the Eastern Ohio Resource Development Center. Regional Science Perspectives, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 25)
  - Place Attributes in a Migration Decision Context. Environment and Planning, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 26)
  - The Adoption of Credit Card Services by Banks: A Case Study of Innovation Diffusion. Bulletin of Business Research The Ohio State University, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 27)
  - Comments on Landscape Evolution and Diffusion Processes. Regional Studies, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 28)
  - The Diffusion of a Population Related Innovation: the Planned Parenthood Affiliate S.S.Q., undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 29)
  - Awareness space Characteristics in a Migration context. Environment and Behavior., undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 30)
  - Acquaintance Circles and Communication: An Exploration of Hypotheses Relating to Innovation Adoption. Professional Geographer, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 31)
  - Cones of Resolution in Spatial Diffusion Studies: A perspective. Professional Geographer, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 32)
  - Adopter Categories in a Spatial Context: Alternative Explanations for an Empirical Regularity. Rural Sociology, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 33)
  - "Regional Changes as the Interplay of Global and Local" The Korean Journal of Applied Geography, 1997 (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 34)
  - "Development Models, Economic Adjustment, and Occupational Composition: Ecuador 1982-90" International Regional Science Review, 1997 (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 35)
  - "Economic Restructuring and Migration in an Old Industrial Region" Migration and Restructuring in the U.S.: A Geographic Perspective, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 36)
  - "Macrolevel Theory and Local-level Inequality: Industrial Structure, Institutional Arrangements…" Annals of the Association of American Geographers, 1999 (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 37)
  - "Employment in boom towns of the Ecuador Amazon" Yearbook of the Association of Pacific Coast Geographers, 1999 (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 38)
  - "Development context, Regional Differences Between Young Women, and Fertility: Ecuadorian Amazon" Social Forces, 1998 (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 39)
  - "Old Industrial Regions and the Political Economy of Development" Rural Restructuring in Local and Global Contexts, 2003 (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 40)
  - "GIS/SA Interface for Substantive Research(ers): A Critical Need" Journal of Geographical Systems, 2000 (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 41)
  - "Urban System Evaluation at the Ecuador Amazon Frontier" Geographical Review, 2000 (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 42)
  - "Urban Development at the Ecuador Amazon Frontier: Boom Towns or Gloom Towns?" Developing Frontier Cities: Global Perspectives, 1999 (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 43)
  - Towards a GeoEd Research Agenda: Observations of Concerned Bystander" Professional Geographer, 1999 (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 44)
  - "Change, Community and the Pursuit of Geographic Understanding, Presidential Address" Annals of the Association of American Geographers, 1999 (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 45)
  - Presidential Musings form the Meridian: Reflections on the Nature of Geography by Past Presidents of the Association of American Geographers., undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 46)
  - "E Willard ‘Will' Miller 1915-2002" Annals of the Association of American Geographers, 2004 (Box UA.2014.0228.0002, Folder 47)
  - Innovation Diffusion in a Developing Economy: A Meso-Scale View. Economic Development and Cultural Change, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 1)
  - Growth Poles, Diffusion, and Development: Comments on Interrelated Work. Latin American Development Issues, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 2)
  - Facility Location under a Maximum Travel Restriction: An Example Using Day Care Facilities. Geographical Analysis, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 3)
  - Diffusion Through an Urban System: The Testing of Related Hypotheses. TIJDSCHRIFT Voor Econ. En Soc. Geografie, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 4)
  - Behavioral Approaches in Geography: An Overview. The Australian Geographer, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 5)
  - Critical Notes on an Alleged Operationalization of the Concept of Spatial Utility. Demography, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 6)
  - Employment Structure as an Indicator of Shifts in the Space Economy. Revista Geografica, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 7)
  - Empirical Regularities in the Diffusion of Innovation. Annals of the Association of American Geographers, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 8)
  - The Delimitation of Functional Regions, Nodal Regions, and Hierarchies by Functional Distance Approaches. Urbanizacao E Regionalizacao, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 9)
  - The Delimitation of Functional Regions, Nodal Regions, and Hierarchies by Functional Distance Approaches. EKISTICS, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 10)
  - The Delimitation of Functional Regions, Nodal Regions, and Hierarchies by Functional Distance Approaches. Journal of Regional Science, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 11)
  - Search Behavior in an Intra-Urban Migration Context: A Spatial Perspective. Environment and Planning, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 12)
  - On Rural Settlement in Israel and Model Strategy. Northern Illinois University Perspectives in Geography, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 13)
  - Intra-Urban Migrant Lifelines: A Spatial View. The Review of Regional Studies, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 14)
  - Intra-Urban Migrant Lifelines: A Spatial View. Demography, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 15)
  - Diffusion of Innovation in Latin America: A Geographer's Perspective. Geographic Research in Latin America: Benchmark, 1970 (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 16)
  - The Intra-Urban Migration Process: A Perspective. Internal Structure of the City, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 17)
  - The Intra-Urban Migration Process: A Perspective. Yearbook of the Society for General Systems Research, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 18)
  - The Intra-Urban Migration Process: A Perspective. Geografiska Annaler, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 19)
  - Migration, Functional Distance, and the Urban Hierarchy. Economic Geography, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 20)
  - Migration Flows in Intra-Urban Space: Place Utility Considerations. Annals of the Association of American Geographers, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 21)
  - Functional Distance: An Operational Approach. Geographical Analysis, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 22)
  - Urban Acquaintance Fields: An Evaluation of a Spatial Model. Environment and Planning, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 23)
  - Urban Activity Systems in a Planning Context. Proceedings of the Environmental Design Research Association Conference., undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 24)
  - Social Area Change: An Empirical Analysis. Urban Studies, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 25)
  - On the Use of Markov Chanis in Movement Research. Economic Geography, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 26)
  - On Place Utility and the Normative Allocation of Intra-Urban Migrants. Demography, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 27)
  - On the Implementation of Place Utility and Related Concepts: The Intra-Urban Migration Case. Behavioral Problems in Geography: A Symposium, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 28)
  - Diffusion Research in Geography: A Perspective. Progress in Geography, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 29)
  - Diffusion of Innovation: A Macro-view. Economic Development and Cultural Change, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 30)
  - Search, Learning, and the Market Decision Process. The Conceptual Revolution in Geography., undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 31)
  - Search, Learning, and the Market Decision Process. Geografisk Annaler, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 32)
  - Diffusion Agency Establishment: The Case of Friendly Ice Cream and Public Sector Diffusion Processes. Socio Economic Planning Sciences, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 33)
  - Proposed Project Aries-6: The Mining Industry and its Relationship to Community Well-Being, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 35)
  - Reprints, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 36-38)
  - Diffusion of Innovation: Markov Chain Approach. Discussion Paper 3, Northwestern, 1963 (Box UA.2014.0228.0003, Folder 39)
  - Latin American Proposal, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 1)
  - NSF Innovation Diffusion Project, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 2)
  - Innovation Diffusion Process in a Public Policy Context. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation #58, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 3)
  - Diffusion Research in Geography, a Thematic Account. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation #53, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 4)
  - Innovation Diffusion and Development in a Third World Setting: The Case of the Cooperative Movement in Sierra Leone. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series #54, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 5)
  - Simulating the Spatial Diffusion of Innovation. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation #55, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 6)
  - Technical Change in the Agricultural Sector: A Problem in Developing Countries. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation #56, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 7)
  - An Economic History Perspective on Innovation Diffusion. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation #51, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 8)
  - Diffusion Agency Establishment in a Mono-Nuclear Setting: The Case of Friendly Ice Cream and Related Considerations. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation #48, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 9)
  - Innovation Establishment in a Rural Setting: Four Case Studies with Reference to a Theoretical Framework. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation #44, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 10)
  - Spatial Diffusion of Innovation: A Gaming Approach. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation #42, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 11)
  - Promar: The New Product Marketing Game. Studies in the Diffusion of Innovation Discussion Paper Series #41, undated (Box UA.2014.0228.0004, Folder 12)